A Guide to the United States Congress: Virginia delegation expenses of representation accounts and vouchers, 1789-1860
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
United States Congress: Virginia delegation expenses of representation accounts and vouchers, 1789-1860
The Library of Virginia
APA 275a
4.75 cu. ft. (11 boxes)
Virginia. Auditor of Public Accounts
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Transferred in 1913.
Scope and Content
This series contains vouchers for the expenses of representing Virginia in Congress. It also contains vouchers for the Presidential electors. Each voucher shows the name of the person owed money, the amount owed, and the date the voucher was submitted.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically.
Contents List
- Accounts and vouchers, 1789 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1790 March-September (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1790 October-December (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1791 April-May (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1791 June-December (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1792 February-June (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1792 September-December (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1793 January-June (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1793 July-December (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1794 February-August (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1794 November-1795 May (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1795 June-December (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1796 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1797 January-June (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1797 September (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1797 October-December (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1798 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1799 January-August (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1799 September (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1799 October-December (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1800 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1801 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1802 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1803 January-September 20 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1803 September 21-30 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1803 October-December (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1804 October-November (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1804 December (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1805 January-June (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1805 August-October (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1805 October-December (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1806 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1807 March-September 21 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1807 September 22-30 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1807 October-December (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1808 January-April (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1808 May-October (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1808 November-December (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1809 January-June (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1809 July-October 24 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1809 October 26-November 8 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1809 November 13-December (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1810 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1811 January-September (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1811 October (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1811 November-December (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1812 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1813 January-October (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1813 November-December (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1814 January-October (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1814 November-December (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1815 January-October (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1815 November-December (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1816 January-October (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1816 November-December (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1817 January-September (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1817 October (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1817 November-December (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1818 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1819 February-October 20 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1819 October 25-December (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1820 February-June (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1820 August-December (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1821 January-October 15 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1821 October 16-31 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1821 November-December (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1822 January-July (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1822 September-December (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1823 January-June (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1823 August-October 31 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1823 November-December (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1824 January-October 23 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1824 October 25-December (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1825 January-September (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1825 October (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1825 November-December (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1833 October (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1833 November (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1833 December (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1834 January-May (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1834 June-October 29 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1834 October 30-December (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1835 March-December (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Accounts and vouchers, 1860 November (Box 11, Folder 5)